- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'A'
    Back: '<em><b>Alpha</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈælfa<br><br>ICAO English respelling: AL fah'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'B'
    Back: '<em><b>Bravo</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈbraːˈvo<br><br>ICAO English respelling: BRAH voh'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'C'
    Back: '<em><b>Charlie</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈtʃɑːli<br><br>ICAO English respelling: CHAR lee'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'D'
    Back: '<em><b>Delta</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈdeltɑ<br><br>ICAO English respelling: DELL tah'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'E'
    Back: '<em><b>Echo</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈeko<br><br>ICAO English respelling: ECK oh'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'F'
    Back: '<em><b>Foxtrot</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈfɔkstrɔt<br><br>ICAO English respelling: FOKS trot'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'G'
    Back: '<em><b>Golf</b></em><br><br>IPA: ɡʌlf<br><br>ICAO English respelling: golf'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'H'
    Back: '<em><b>Hotel</b></em><br><br>IPA: hoːˈtel<br><br>ICAO English respelling: ho TELL'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'I'
    Back: '<em><b>India</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈindi.ɑ<br><br>ICAO English respelling: IN dee ah'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'J'
    Back: '<em><b>Juliett</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈdʒuːli.ˈet<br><br>ICAO English respelling: JEW lee ETT'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'K'
    Back: '<em><b>Kilo</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈkiːlo<br><br>ICAO English respelling: KEY loh'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'L'
    Back: '<em><b>Lima</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈliːmɑ<br><br>ICAO English respelling: LEE mah'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'M'
    Back: '<em><b>Mike</b></em><br><br>IPA: mɑik<br><br>ICAO English respelling: mike'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'N'
    Back: '<em><b>November</b></em><br><br>IPA: noˈvembə<br><br>ICAO English respelling: no VEM ber'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'O'
    Back: '<em><b>Oscar</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈɔskɑ<br><br>ICAO English respelling: OSS cah'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'P'
    Back: '<em><b>Papa</b></em><br><br>IPA: pəˈpɑ<br><br>ICAO English respelling: pah PAH'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Q'
    Back: '<em><b>Quebec</b></em><br><br>IPA: keˈbek<br><br>ICAO English respelling: keh BECK'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'R'
    Back: '<em><b>Romeo</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈroːmi.o<br><br>ICAO English respelling: ROW me oh'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'S'
    Back: '<em><b>Sierra</b></em><br><br>IPA: siˈerɑ<br><br>ICAO English respelling: see AIR rah'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'T'
    Back: '<em><b>Tango</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈtænɡo<br><br>ICAO English respelling: TANG go'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'U'
    Back: '<em><b>Uniform</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈjuːnifɔːm<br><br>ICAO English respelling: YOU nee form'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'V'
    Back: '<em><b>Victor</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈviktɑ<br><br>ICAO English respelling: VIK tah'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'W'
    Back: '<em><b>Whiskey</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈwiski<br><br>ICAO English respelling: WISS key'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'X'
    Back: '<em><b>X-ray</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈeksˈrei<br><br>ICAO English respelling: ECKS ray'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Y'
    Back: '<em><b>Yankee</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈjænki<br><br>ICAO English respelling: YANG key'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Z'
    Back: '<em><b>Zulu</b></em><br><br>IPA: ˈzuːluː<br><br>ICAO English respelling: ZOO loo'
